ACTWU New England Regional Joint Board Records 5619/045
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration decisions. (Box 2)
  - Arbitration Decision, Dye Craftsmen, Antonio DaVeiga, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Arbitrator Garry J. Wooters; August 21 1989
  - Arbitration Decision, Dye Craftsmen, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Cabral discharge, January 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    6-hour grievance; Arbitrator Litton; August 23 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Carlos Visinho warning; Arbitrator Litton; November 21 1983
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    6-hour case
  - Maintenance of Earnings, Cliftex, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    James Litton, Esquire; August 15 1985
  - Cliftex Corporation, Settled Arbitrations, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cliftex Corporation Appeal, Maria L. Pires, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Settles arbitration; J. Hudson; June 1991
  - Cliftex vs. ACTWU Grievance, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Operation 17; July 1992
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Vacation pay-wage increase; March 1986
  - Cliftex Corporation, Blockers Grievances, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Sides and backs pressers; Litton; July 1983
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Employees discharge without reasonable cause; Litton; August 1982
  - Cliftex, Settles Arbitrations, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Felling sides, December 1982; Fuser, February 25 1983
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Plant A blocking and pinching departments; June 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, Plant B, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Rates, plaids vs. solids; May 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, Plant A, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Rates, top stitchers; April 1980
  - Cliftex Plant A, Luis Carvalho, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Phillip Ross; Arbitrator Job Bid; December 1989
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Operation Fl. Fusing fronts; Riverside Fusers; December 1983
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, L4, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Piece rates, hand ironers, reporting pay; November 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Operation 8, B2 and 27 rates; August 15 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Cliftex, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Mello, Sedgwick IRIA, discharges; Litton; July 1983
  - Calvin Clothing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Maria F. Andrade seniority; Professor Horowitz; December 15 1992
  - Calvin Clothing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Discharge of Shawn Roberts; Professor Horowitz; December 15 1992
  - Calvin Clothing, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Armindo DeMello, Maintenance of earnings; Professor Horowitz; May 30 1991
  - Calvin Clothing, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Antonio Nunes; Arbitrator Morris Horowitz; June 22 1989
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Esperanca DeJesus; March 2 1988
  - Calvin Clothing, Settled Arbitrations, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Tom Haskins piece rate; Horowitz; July 1984
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Alzira Da Silva; March 31 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Grievance of block/label pressers; May 1979
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Jose Areias; July 1977
  - Arbitration Decision, Calvin Clothing, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    G. Vieira, July 4th holiday pay; Horowitz; December 1984
  - Appeal, Manuela Condeco, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Hearing officer Tony Costanza; February 2 1990
  - Cape Cod Sportswear, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    David Branco, suspension; Professor M. Horowitz; October 5 1994
  - Settled Arbitration, Cape Cod Sportswear, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Maria Melo, pay cut; Professor Horowitz; February 17 1994
  - Arbitration Decision, Bradley Scott, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Gonsalves, holiday pay calculation; May 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Bradley Scott and ACTWU Negotiations, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    May 21 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Bradley Scott, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Deminico, traveling allowances and piece rate; July 1986
  - Settled Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Peter Quintal, Allen Quintal and Diane Tobiaz; July 1983
  - Arbitration decision, Bradley Scott, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Pieceworker holiday pay
  - Arbitration Award, Bixby International, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Pro-rata vacation pay; Arbitrator Klitzman; October 30 1991
  - Bixby International Corporation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Grievance filed by Kenneth Volak
  - Arbitration, Asher Winer Corp. and Local 309, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Professor Horowitz; November 15 1993
  - Arbitration Decision, Asher Co., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Piece rates; arbitrator Professor Horowitz; March 16 1992
  - Arbitration Opinion and Award, Asher Co., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Hiring outside of the bargaining agreement; Arbitrator Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Asher Co., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Suspension of Avant and Crosby; Arbitrator Horowitz; March 6 1986
  - Settled, Ernie Infantino and Asher Co., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    June 1983
  - Gil Falala Hearing, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    May 3 1994, 4:00 PM; Lawrence Office
  - Arbitration Decision, Anderson-Little Corp., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Manuela Vieira discharge; March 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, Anderson-Little Tailors, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Sick pay
  - Arbitration Decision, Anderson-Little, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Absentee discharge; Arbitrator Pinkus
  - Arbitration Opinion and Award, American London, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Discharge of Albert Woodson; Arbitrator Horowitz; January 1994
  - Arbitration Opinion and Award, American London, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Absenteeism of Bob Duran; Arbitrator Horowitz; October 13 1993
  - Settled Arbitration, American London, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Robert LeBlanc
  - Arbitration Decision, American London-Norwood, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Michael Ward; November 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, American London-Norwood, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Van van Pham; December 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, American London-Norwood, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Contract exhibits 2 and 3; August 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, American London-Norwood, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Scima and Muller; July 1984
  - File on Arbitrator Professor Morris A. Horowitz (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Edward Clark (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Cliftex Plant A, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Piece rates for 1978 Finished coat pressing
  - File on Arbitrator Millard Cass (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - File on Arbitrator James M. Litton, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - File on Arbitrator Edward Pinkus, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - File on Arbitrator Philip Ross, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Arbitration Appeals Standard Letter (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Local 125 Executive Board, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Local 177 Executive Board Rulings, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Local 667 Executive Board Rulings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Local 725 Kay Torrey, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Local 377 Executive Board, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Finance Committee (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Insurance Arbitration, Whiting CO., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Arbitrator Cass; May 23 1984
  - Arbitration Decision, E.B. and A.C. Whiting Company, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Mandatory overtime (Section 9e); February 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, E.B. and A.C. Whiting Company, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Roving maintenance employment made permanent; Arbitrator Nadworny
  - Arbitration Decision, E.B. and A.C. Whiting Company, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Vi-Mil, Inc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Arbitration Decision, Vi-Mil Inc., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Insurance fund; Arbitrator Horowitz; April 10 1984
  - Arbitration Decision, van Baalen, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Cutters; Local 371 and 4 Jurisdiction; Arbitrator Gray
  - Arbitration Decision, Swiss Art, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    October 14 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Standard Coat Apron and Linen Service, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    Application of general wage increase clause; June 21 1960
  - Arbitration Decision, Standard Linen, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    May Brewster discharge; Arbitrator Hogan
  - Arbitration Decision, Sova Outerwear, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    Retroactive pay for Lillian Benoit; April 1972
  - Arbitration Decision, Sova Outerwear, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    Holiday and vacation pay; April 1 1982
  - Insurance Arbitration; Shutzer Manufacturing, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Arbitration Decision, Shelburne Shirt, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    Laurie Melo, transferred employee; February 1982
  - Arbitration Decision, Shelburne, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Laurie Melo; February 1982
  - Arbitration Decision, Shelburne Shirt, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Piece rates, final trim
  - Arbitration Decision, Shelburne Shirt, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    Settled agreement time study; August 1979
  - Settled Arbitrations, Shelburne Shirt, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - San-Toro, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    Vacation pay grievance; October 1990
  - Arbitration Decision, San-Toro, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    Almeida discharge; Arbitrator Horowitz
  - Samoset Processing, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Arbitration Decision, Samoset Processing, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Arbitration Decision, Samoset, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    Seniority, article XXXV; Arbitrator Cass; October 26 1982
  - Settlement Agreement, Riverside Manufacturing, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    Rachael Rebello; Arbitrator Leonard Schneider; December 21 1995
  - Settlement Agreement, Riverside Manufacturing, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    Otilia Rodriguez; December 2000
  - Arbitration Decision and Award, Riverside Manufacturing, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Christmas and vacation pay; December 1989
  - Riverside Manufacturing and Local 377, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Termination of Jose Furtado
  - Riverside Manufacturing and Local 377, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Joao Andrade; Arbitrator Morris Horowitz; February 25 1999
  - Arbitration Opinion and decision, Riverside Manufacturing, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    Discharge of Orlando M. Batista
  - Arbitration, Nu-Wear, Inc., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    Holiday pay; Arbitrator Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Nu-Wear, Inc., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    Panariti Discharge; Arbitrator Horowitz; June 1979
  - Forecaster, Inc., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Mostly agreements. (Box 3)
  - Union Opinion and Agreement, Domani Clothing Manufacturing Corp., 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agreements and Supplemental Agreements between Darwood Manufacturing and the ACTW Union, AFL-CIO, 1959-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agreements and Supplemental Agreement between Bradley Scott and Gramatan Clothes and ACWA, 1968-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Information Regarding the ACTW Union and Pioneer Parachute Company, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agreements between Anderson-Little Co., Inc. and the ACWA Union, 1940-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anderson-Little Co. Tailors, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Agreements between the parties; Arbitrator Horowitz
  - Agreements between Shelburne Shirt Company and ACWA Union, 1951-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Agreements between Essex Manufacturing Company and ACTW Union, 1958-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agreements between San-Toro Manufacturing Corp. and ACWA Union, 1965-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Relations between Riverside Manufacturing Co. and ACTW Union, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Information on Sova Outerwear Corp. and ACTW Union, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Agreements and Communication between Sova Outerwear Corp. and ACWA Union, 1959-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Communication and Agreements between ACWA and Arlan's Department Stores, 1965-1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ratification of Contracts, Dues Increase, Letters to Employers on Dues Increase, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
  - Industrial Department, Harry Lautman, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - ACTWU and Gerber Cutting Machine, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Mostly agreements. (Box 4)
  - Agreements and Communication between Brand Rex Co. and ACTW Union, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - University of Connecticut Pension Plan, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Amgraph Packaging Inc. Pension Plan and Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1987-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ensign-Bickford Industries and Local 687T, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    1995 Collective bargaining agreement language disputes
  - Agreement Between J.H. Horne and Sons Co. and ACTW Union, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Armtec Industries and the ACTW Union (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - West Point Pepperell Rates and Communications, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bernise Coulombe (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - West Point Pepperell Comb or merge Jobs, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Temporary Lack of Work West Point Pepperell, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - West Point Pepperell Monthly Piece Work Averages, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - West Point Pepperell Piece Work Group Averages, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - West Point Pepperrell Seniority List, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Letter to West Point Pepperell, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Letter from West Point Pepperell, 1984-2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Membership cards for Local 183. (Box 5)
  - Employee Identification Cards (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Restricted
- Local 183 Benefits. (Box 6)
  - Employee Identification Cards (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Local 1069. (Box 7)
  - Gentlemen's Warehouse 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ACTWU 1069 Convention Nominations and Elections, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ACTWU Local 1069 Convention Nominations and Elections, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gentlemen's Wear House Store List, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Opt Outs Gentlemen's Wear House (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gentlemen's Wear House Important Items, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gentlemen's Wear House, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ACTWU Local 1069, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Amalgamated Bank of NY
  - Local 1609, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - ACTWU Local 1609, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Men's Wear House, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Surveys for Christmas Party, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Surveys, Gentlemen's Wear House (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Grievances Gentlemen's Wear House, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell Smith (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gentlemen's Wear House, Springfield, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Meetings regarding grievances
  - Suspension of Sid Aaron, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Depalma, Henry, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kenneth Millward, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Employee and management statements
  - Griffin, John, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Reports on the termination of John Griffin
  - Doug Munger, GW Auburn, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Grievances report
  - Gentlemen's Wear House, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    ACTWU Local 1069 Surveys
  - Anderson-Little Health Insurance Survey, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    May 1994
  - Amalgamated Bank of NY, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ACTWU Local 1069, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ACTWU Local 1069, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Turcotte vs. Anderson-Little, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    9/6/1996
  - Signed Contract Cliftex Corporation, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Anderson-Little Company Policies, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Anderson-Little Store List, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Local 1069 Labor Management Reports, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Anderson-Little Contract Negotiations, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    May 1994; Expire April 1997
  - Anderson-Little Contract Negotiation Correspondence, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Dale Barry, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Rogers, Paul, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Anderson-Little Survey Contract, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Nominations and Elections of Negotiating Committee ACTWU Local 1069, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - John Liner Members and Dependents, Disability Claims, Policies Issued, Death Claims, 1959-1979 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Bound book
  - Cash Disbursements, 1973-1983 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Bound Book
  - Steps for Various Cloth Items, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Large printouts detailing steps of production
- Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Andover Shop, 1965-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    127 Main Street, Andover, Massachusetts 01810
  - American London, Wage agreements and communications, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Associated Textile Rental Services, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bradley Scott, Letters Proposals and Agreements, 1981-1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Biddeford Textile, Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bixby, Shoe Division, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Brooks Brothers, 1977-1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    46 Newbury Street, Boston, Massachusetts
  - Dye Craftsmen, Contract negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Negotiation Notes, Fall River Shirt, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fall River Shirts, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Fall River Shirt, Contracts and Communication, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - William Filene's, Agreements and Communications, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - William Filene's, Agreements and Communications, 1982-1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - C.F. Hathaway Company, Agreements and Communications, 1978-1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Louis, Inc., Memorandums of Understanding, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    470 Boylston Street, Boston, Massachusetts, 02167
  - Employers in Multiemployer Group with Men's Alterations Departments, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Milton's Contract and Communications, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - New England Clothing, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - J. Press, Inc., Communications and Memorandums, 1974-1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Riverside, Small Claims Complaint, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Riverside, GFT Newspaper Clippings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Riverside Manufacturing Negotiations, 1987-1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Riverside Manufacturing Negotiations, 1977-1987 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - San-Toro Manufacturing, Union Agreement, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Standard Coat, Apron and Linen Services, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    March 4 1982
  - Sterlingwear of Boston, Contract Negotiations, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Swiss-Art, Brittany Dye, Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Swiss-Art Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Tartan Textile Co., Supplemental Agreement, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - van Baalen Negotiations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - van Baalen Time Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - West Point Pepperell, Inc., Memorandum of Agreement, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - E.B. and A.C. Whiting, Contract Negotiations, 1952-1988 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Yale-Genton Clothes, Inc., Arbitration Disputes, 1982-1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    1130 Riverdale Street, W. Springfield, Massachusetts
  - Yale-Genton, Agreements and Communications, 1953-1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Agreements (Box 9)
  - American London-Norwood, 1980-1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Andover Shop and Local 2521 New England Regional Joint Board, 1965-2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Associates Textile Rental Services, Agreements, 1987-1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Biddeford Mill, West Point Pepperell, Agreements, 1987-1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bixby International Corp., Agreement, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bradley Scott, Agreements, 1985-1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bradley Scott Clothes, Agreements, 1968-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Brooks Brothers, Agreement, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Central Operations, Agreement and Memorandums of Understanding, 1969-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dye Craftsmen, Agreement, 1979-1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Fall River Shirt, Agreement, 1988-1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - William Filene's, Memorandums of Agreement, 1983-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - William Filene Sons Co., Agreements, 1954-1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Arthur H. Freedberg, Agreements, 1980-1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Cooperative Society, Agreement, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - C.F. Hathaway Co., Agreements, 1970-1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Agreements (Box 10)
  - C.F. Hathaway, Agreements, 1945-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Justin Clothing, Agreements, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Justin Clothing, agreement, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Justin Clothing, Agreement, 1953-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, Inc., Agreement, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Louis, Inc., Agreements, 1971-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lujon's Men's Clothes, Inc., agreement, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lyn-Del Corporation, Agreement, 1952-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Marv Sportswear, 1975-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - R.J. McCartney, Supplemental Agreement, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Milton's, Agreements, 1971-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - George Morrell, Agreement, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - National Linen Service, Agreement, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - J. Press, Agreements, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Riverside Manufacturing, agreements and communications, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Riverside Manufacturing, agreements, 1980-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Riverside Manufacturing, agreement, 1957-1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Saco Defense, Inc., Agreements, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - San-Toro Manufacturing, agreement, 1961-1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sketchley Services, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Agreements (Box 11)
  - Standard Coat, Apron, and Linen Service, agreements, 1959-1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - State Coat Front, 1979-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreements
  - Sterlingwear of Boston, 1986-1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - M.J. Sullivan, agreements, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Swiss-Art, agreements, 1979-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - van Baalen Pacific, agreements, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - van Baalen Pacific, agreements, 1981-1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - van Baalen Pacific, agreements, 1939-1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Warnaco Men's Apparel, Local Issues Agreement, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - E.B. and A.C. Whiting, agreements, 1980-1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - E.B. and A.C. Whiting, agreement, 1956-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Yale-Genton Clothes, agreements, 1948-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Blank Agreements, 1983-1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Blank Agreements, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)